<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://aossmedicalsupply.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://aossmedicalsupply.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://aossmedicalsupply.com/collections/bathroom-cleaning-supplies.atom"/>
  <title>AOSS Medical Supply</title>
  <updated>2019-06-10T13:11:50-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>AOSS Medical Supply</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/3760089694242</id>
    <published>2019-06-10T13:11:50-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-10T13:11:50-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/long-lasting-urinal-screen-and-deodorizer-with-non-para-block-12-pack-universal-fit-citrus-scent-cake-releases-cleaning-agents-to-remove-odor"/>
    <title>Urinal Screen and Deodorizer with Non-Para Block 12 Pack. Universal-Fit, Citrus-Scent Cake Releases Cleaning Agents To Remove Odor</title>
    <s:type>Urinal Screen</s:type>
    <s:vendor>AOSS Medical Supply</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2545/6632/products/14b93744-b7c6-497e-8248-f28ad2b41d05_1.8fe8f340f883dce8c16a1b8e9d9e57c3.jpeg?v=1560363862"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>AOSS Medical Supply<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Urinal Screen<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            32.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Not only do they smell great, but Mop Mob’s urinal screens are made with a 3 oz block that releases cleaning agents with each flush. Simply place the easy to install, long lasting screen in your school, business, restaurant, or office’s urinal and let our product do the cleaning for you. Replace the screen whenever the cake stops releasing a colored liquid when you flush the urinal.<br><br>Buying our 12 pack of long lasting, great smelling screens lets you worry about the important things like building your business, instead of the minor things like is my urinal clean or am I going to run out of blocks. Stock up with our bulk deal so that you can save money, have more time to do what you want, and have your urinals require less work.<br><br>Due to the anti-bacterial design and the urine splash-back prevention keeping employees from tracking urine throughout the building our customers have reported an increase in employee health since they began using our product. Helping to keep employees healthy ensures that you get their best work and that workers take fewer sick days.<br><br>Our screens are designed to be usable in any common urinals. Buy with confidence knowing that changing out our urinal screens will be a piece of cake.<br><br>If you aren’t completely satisfied with your order, simply reach out to us through the Amazon messaging service and we will respond within 24 hours to make it right even on the weekends. We absolutely guarantee your satisfaction or your money back!</p>
<ul>
<li>CLEANS WITH EACH FLUSH! Our heavy-duty citrus scented block releases surfactants and chelates with each flush to clean and deodorize urinals so you don’t have to worry on busy nights.</li>
<li>PREMIUM DESIGN PREVENTS DEBRIS FROM CAUSING COSTLY CLOGS. The flexible screen keeps gum, trash, and other debris often dropped into urinals from entering the drain and causing damaging clogs.</li>
<li>EVEN THE HIGHEST VOLUME URINAL WILL BE ODOR-FREE. The powerful, citrus scented block reliably neutralizes odors that build up in busy restrooms.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>urinal</s:tag>
    <s:tag>urinal cake</s:tag>
    <s:tag>urinal cleaning</s:tag>
    <s:tag>urinal odor</s:tag>
    <s:tag>urinal screen</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/3760089694242</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>800006</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6804</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/3760061513762</id>
    <published>2019-06-10T12:48:53-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-10T12:48:53-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/clorox-disinfecting-toiletwand-refill-heads"/>
    <title>Clorox Disinfecting ToiletWand Refill Heads</title>
    <s:type>Toilet Cleaner</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Clorox</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2545/6632/products/ff562c90b85415e47648a33e36fb8fe650.jpg?v=1560363849"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Clorox<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Toilet Cleaner<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            37.54
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div>
<p>Clorox Disinfecting ToiletWand Refill Heads, 6/Pack - Refill includes six disposable heads for the Clorox Toilet Wand Cleaning Kit. These disposable heads kill germs and clean your toilet bowl quickly, easily and with zero mess. Preloaded with Clorox toilet bowl cleaner, these disinfecting cleaning heads power through stains while they kill 99.9 percent of germs like staphylococcus aureus, salmonella enterica, rhinovirus type 37 and Influenza A. The spongy cleaning refills conform to surfaces and scrub hard-to-reach places, even under the rim. Simply click a toilet-cleaning head in place, swish the toilet bowl and toss the disposable head into the trash bin when you're done. Refill head measures 2-1/2 x 2-1/2" x 1-1/4"."</p>
</div>
<ul class="styled-list">
<li>Unique design for hygienic use and disposal—eliminates the need to store a dirty, germ-ridden toilet brush.</li>
<li>Sponge-like head conforms to the toilet bowl to clean hard-to-reach places.</li>
<li>Disposable cleaning head comes preloaded with concentrated Clorox® foaming cleaner for fresh refill each time.</li>
<li>48/CS</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>clorox</s:tag>
    <s:tag>toilet bowl</s:tag>
    <s:tag>toilet bowl cleaner</s:tag>
    <s:tag>toilet wand</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://aossmedicalsupply.com/products/3760061513762</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.54</s:price>
      <s:sku>CLO14882CT</s:sku>
      <s:grams>4082</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
